[{"answer": "Yeah. What, is it a problem", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Well, I guess he figured you just wouldn't care. It", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No, you're not a divorcee. You're just separated. You'r", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, you're not out there", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah, so", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What move", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "He did the move", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You know..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What move", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Wait a second.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Are you sure", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I can't believe it. He", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Isn't that a little...rash", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah, but..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah. The pinch.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I know, he's probably the only honest mechanic in that place.", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "All right, all right. Here. ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You feel better", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You're gonna tell me...or not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I got a headboard", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah. my friend, my friend. I'm my friend, the my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh, hi, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What move", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hey, what's the story? I hear you're doing my move", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What move?", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What move", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You're move? What, are you kidding? I was doing that before I knew you. All you told me about was the ending", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You're move? What, are you kidding? I was doing that before I knew you. All you told me about was the ending", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, that ending was", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Swirl", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, yeah, I know. You do the", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, stop it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No. I don't", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You must have done", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Oh my god. Yes, you close with the swirl. There's a progression there. I told you to write it down", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Supposed to close with the swirl", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yeah, yeah, should've written it down.", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " What? What is this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Getting an eye job like some Manhattanite, huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend made a pass at you? You're crazy", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Well, it's already working. my friend made a pass at me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm not crazy. He stopped short and made a grab", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "my friend made a pass at you? You're crazy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "He stopped short? That's my move. I'm gonna kill him!", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Nothing, nothing. I'm just taking an interest in what you...do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Oh...any kind o", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Sixteen hundred dollars? That's all?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Well, that's it. I'm going back to Putty. No move is worth this", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "In a car, with my wife. He stopped short. You think I don't know what that's about? That's my old move! I used it on my friend forty years ago! I told everybody about it! Everybody knows!  Hmmph! I stopped short", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "You're not kidding it's a good move!", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "C'mon, my friend, relax. I don't even know what you're talking about.", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Don't Frank me! I know what you did. How dare you stop short with my wife", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You think I don't know, my friend?!! To think I almost split the profits on the Manssierre with you", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "The name on the boat. Look at it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Fusilli-Jerry.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "Yeah , he's the Assman! my friend,", "qsentId": 58}]